你看到了吗
Did you see it?
她知道吗
Does she know?
千万别让她知道了
This is the last thing she needs today.
别看
No!
今天邓菲家可忙了
Busy day at the Dunphy compound.
晚上要参加婚礼
We have a wedding tonight,
下午克莱尔要和杜恩·贝利辩论
and this afternoon, Claire is debating Duane Bailey
竞选镇议员
in the race for town council.
而现在 《每周救星》报上说
And now the "Weekly Saver" says
一些选民认为克莱尔
that some voters find Claire-- quote--
"脾气暴躁 讨人嫌"
"Angry and unlikable."
我想对这些选民说
To those voters, I say,
"等她发现了 再让你们见识真正的暴躁"
"Wait till she sees this."
千万别告诉她
No one can mention it to her.
不能让这些无厘头的民意调查
We can't have some unscientific poll
打击克莱尔的信心
shaking Claire's confidence.
菲尔
Phil...
-什么民调 -完了 她知道了
- What poll? -Too late. She knows.
谁告诉她的
Who told her?
-干嘛 要搞政治迫害吗 -我的天啊
- What is this, a witch hunt? - Oh, my god.
我得挂了
I have to go.
我觉得这没啥大不了的
Well, I just don't think it's a big deal.
没多少人会读这《每周...》叫啥来着
I mean, how many people read the "Weekly..."
-《救星》 -《救星》 随便吧
- "Saver"? -"Saver," anyway?
22000左右吧
22,000... ish.
我们公司
My company adver--
曾经在这报纸上登过广告
used to advertise with that newspaper.
我怎么就脾气暴躁兼讨人嫌了
And how am I angry and unlikable?
我能回答这个问题吗
Can I take this one?
劝你别
I wouldn't.
你现在就很暴躁
You seem angry now.
是这民意调查惹的
I am angry, at that poll.
我觉得是因为你大吼大叫 说话得温柔点儿
I think it's the yelling. I would tone down the yelling.
宝贝 我不会无缘无故大吼
Honey, I don't yell for no reason.
老师说我"与众不同" 你就冲她吼
You yelled at my teacher for calling me "special."
宝贝 她那不是夸你
Honey, that was not a compliment.
-亲 你不讨人嫌 -谢谢
- Sweetheart, you're not unlikable. - Thank you.
你只是看起来讨人嫌
You just seem unlikable.
但如果我们努把力 问题就能解决
But if we work on it, it's totally fixable.
怎么解决 菲尔 我们怎么"努把力"
How? How, Phil? How are we gonna "Work on it"?
首先 收收你这脾气
First of all, lose the snippy attitude.
然后 要不我们来个模拟辩论吧
And I don't know--maybe we could have a mock debate.
好主意
Oh. Good idea.
这样一来 妈就可以演练一下发表政见了
That way, mom can rehearse her views on the issues.
是啊 而且我们可以帮她指出
Yeah, and we can point out all the little things
不讨选民喜欢的小细节
she does that turn people off.
比如这副表情 你得改改
Like that look. I would lose that look.
看得我发毛 不过好多了
Spooky, but better.
好的 非常感谢
All right. Thank you very much.
嘿 莉莉 快过来 宝贝
Hey, Lily! Come here, honey!
嗨 你知道这是什么吗
Hi! Do you know what this is?
是盒子
A box.
-裹着什么 -她不懂"裹着"这个词
- Containing? -She doesn't know "containing."
就得这样教她新词汇 言传身教
Well, that's how she learns new words, by us using them.
你整天灌输一些超难词汇
Or, that's how we lower her self-esteem,
也可能打击她的自尊啊
by bombarding her with confusing vocabulary.
盒子里裹着什么
What's the box containing?
说了吧
Told you.
好吧 是你的裙子
Okay. It's your dress.
终于送到了
It's finally here!
每个小女孩都梦想着
It's every little girl's dream
成为婚礼上的花童
to be a flower girl in a wedding.
这是莉莉大放异彩的机会
It's Lily's chance to shine.
我做过三次捧戒指的戒童
I was a 3-time ring bearer.
这是莉莉大放异彩的机会
It's lily's chance to shine.
真漂亮
Pretty!
哦不 小卡
Oh, no, Cam--
小卡 穿这身她会像牧羊女小波波
Cam, she's gonna look like little bo peep.
或是牧羊女穷波波
Or little bo cheap.
看这料子 都已经起毛球了
Look at this fabric. It's already pilling.
穿上身可能会好看点儿
Maybe it look better on?
你是说把灯开上吗
You mean turned on?
不 不行 小卡啊
No, it does not--Cam!
我喜欢
I love it!
不 不喜欢
No, you don't.
我的天 我们真的要给她穿这个吗
Oh, my gosh. Are we really gonna let her wear this?
如果新娘想来场俗气婚礼
You know what? If the bride wants to have a tacky wedding,
就让她俗气去吧
She can have a tacky wedding.
-咱家莉莉就成"亮"点了 -够"亮"的
- Lily will be the bright spot. - Literally.
说出来就后悔了
Heard it as soon as I said it.
斯黛拉
Stella!
我的小乖乖呢
Where's my good girl?
歌洛莉亚 斯黛拉在楼上吗
Gloria, is stella up there?
不在 但我在
No. But I am.
你回家怎么不跟自己老婆打招呼呢
Why don't you say "hello" your wife when you come home?
那你怎么不在门口摇着尾巴迎接我呢
Well, why don't you greet me at the door, wagging your tail?
斯黛拉 宝贝 你在哪儿
Stella, honey! Where are you?
斯黛拉
Stella!
我的宝贝啊
My baby!
斯黛拉 我来啦 我来啦
Stella, I'm coming! I'm coming!
你没事吧 没事吧
You okay? You okay?
你怎么穿着衣服游泳啊
Why are you swimming in your clothes?
身材太差 不好意思穿泳裤出来秀
Because I'm self-conscious about my body.
斯黛拉掉进池子里了
Stella fell in the pool.
都是我不好 我放她出来
It's my fault. I let her out,
然后我忙着弄优惠券 走不开
and then I got caught up in my couponing.
有游泳课的优惠券吗
Any coupons for swim lessons?
斯黛拉得学学
'Cause Stella needs some.
有没搞错啊 你教曼尼学游泳
Seriously? Manny you teach to swim
就是把他扔水里自己扑腾
by throwing him in the pool,
却让狗去参加游泳班
but the dog gets swimming lessons?
我得说 那么学虽然痛苦 但很有效
I gotta say, it was unpleasant but effective.
我们必须教会斯黛拉游泳
We have to teach Stella how to swim.
不然 她会淹死的
Otherwise, she could drown.
你为啥不教她别往池子里跳呢
Why don't you teach her not to jump in the pool?
她不是跳下去的 她是掉下去的
She didn't jump in the pool. She fell in the pool.
如果她不会游泳
Why, suddenly, would she jump in the pool
怎么会突然跳进池子呢
when she doesn't know how to swim?
那她为什么冲着吸尘器叫呢
Why does she bark at the vacuum?
吸尘器是个东西 永远不会跟你玩的
It's a thing. It is never going to play with you.
你是说斯黛拉蠢吗
Are you saying that Stella is stupid?
你这是捂着她耳朵吗
Are you covering her ears?
有点儿同情心好吧
Let's have a little compassion.
她刚死里逃生 还心有余悸呢
She's probably still traumatized from her near-death experience.
又来了 搞什么啊
Again? What's happening?!
别
Ay, no!
欢迎两位候选人 邓菲太太
Welcome, candidates. Mrs. Dunphy...
感谢给我这个机会
Thank you for having me.
还有贝利议员
And councilman Bailey.
谢谢你 艾丽克斯
Gosh, thank you so much, Alex.
很荣幸能站在这里
I'm deeply honored to be here,
我将一如既往地为人民服务
and I remain, as ever, a humble servant
为我们最伟大的小镇
to the greatest little town
在这最棒的
in the greatest darn--
翻白眼
Eye-rolling.
我翻着玩儿的
Playful eye rolling.
我们选民哪会知道你是玩儿 我觉得这不好
How do we, as voters, know it's playful? I would avoid it.
好 不翻白眼
Okay. No eye rolling.
而且别这么抿嘴
And don't purse your lips like that.
看起来像生气了
It makes you look annoyed.
而且别摸脸
And don't touch your face.
是啊 别摸脸 这样显得紧张
Yeah, no face touching. Seems nervous.
你们这太主观了
Some of this is subjective.
-又怎么了 -你发脾气了
- What? What now? - Anger.
你似乎在指责我们
It looks like you're scolding us.
那我这么叉着腰吧
I will keep my hands at my sides.
别叉屁股上 你不是超人
Not on your hips. You're not superman.
我们能开始了吗
Can we get started?
我们还没开始吗
We haven't started?
我准备了些问题
I've prepared some questions.
哦 太好了 还真有问题
Oh, goody! Actual questions.
-喇叭警告 讽刺 -赶紧提问吧
- Honk. Sarcasm. - Just go.
好吧 邓菲夫人
Okay, Mrs. Dunphy,
您为什么要竞选镇议员呢
why are you running for local office?
好吧 那个 问得很好
Okay, that's, um, that's good.
我 那个 我
I... um, I--
老妈 你应该把这些基本问题
Mom, you really shouldn't stutter
准备得滚瓜烂熟才行
over a basic question like that.
至少你得搞清自己竞选的理由
You should at least know why you're running.
主持人不是应该持中立态度吗
I thought the moderator was supposed to be objective.
谁让我是这里唯一
Not if she's the only one in the room
有过辩论经验的人
who has actual debate experience.
再问一次 为什么参选
Now why are you running?
我发现这个社区需要一个停车路标
I saw the need for a stop sign in--
骗子
Liar!
菲尔
Phil!
我觉得你要准备好应付各种突发状况
I-I just think you should be ready for anything.
我发现这个社区需要一个
I saw the need for a s--
怎么了
What?
不好意思 手滑了一下
Sorry. Accidental buzz.
我发现这个社区需要一个停车路标
I saw the need for a stop sign in my neighborhood,
但即使我收集了必须的区民签名支持
and although I collected the necessary signatures
并备齐了文件材料 我发现镇政府
and did the paperwork, I found local government
依然无视此事
to be entirely unhelpful--
-当我 又怎么了 -句子太长 让我觉得无聊
- When--what? - Too long. I'm bored.
对 下个问题吧 感觉跟上课似的
Yeah, next question. I feel like I'm in school.
有人认为 我们的政治体制
Some say the political system is bogged down
就是被一些思想强硬派的
by ideological hard-liners
不妥协政策给拖了后腿
unwilling to compromise.
贝利议员 您如何回应这种说法
How would you respond to that, councilman Bailey?
我得求救了
I would like to use my lifeline.
我来回答
I'll take this.
如果我当选 我会尊重各方观点
If elected, I would consider all perspectives,
而且绝不会无视反对意见
and I would not ignore opposing viewpoints.
救援直升机来了 你继续
Helicopter. Just keep going.
我会尊重各方观点
I would consider all perspectives,
-而且绝不会无视反对 -下去吧
- and I wouldn't ignore opposing-- - You suck!
卢克
Luke!
你得准备好应付起哄者
You have to be ready for hecklers.
没错
He's right.
好的 从头再来 不准打断
Okay. I'm doing over. No buzzing.
如果我当选 我
If elected, I--
-又怎么了 -离麦克风太近了
- What? - Too close to the mic.
菲尔 这是个梳子
Phil, it's a hairbrush.
好吧
Okay.
如果我当选 我会尊重各方观点
If elected, I would consider all opinions
而且绝不会无视反对意见
and not ignore those of the opposition,
绝不会步贝利议员六届任期施政的后尘
as councilman Bailey has done for six terms.
又怎么了 我回答得多棒
What? That was a great answer.
好吧 我听不下去了
Well, I couldn't hear it
因为你把不好看的半边脸面向了观众
because you were showing me the bad side of your face.
我有半边脸不好看吗
I have a bad side?
-对 左半边 -不对 是右半边
- Yeah, the left. - No. It's the right.
老爸 绝对是左半边好吧 你自己看看
Uh, dad, it's totally the left. I mean, look at it.
宝贝 我选择睡左边是有道理的
Sweetheart, why do you think I chose my side of the bed?
好吧 谢谢你们了
Okay! Okay. Thank you.
谢谢我亲爱的家人们 你们真是帮了我一个"大忙"
Thank you, family. This has been super-duper helpful.
手势 嘴唇 讽刺 翻白眼
Hands, lips, sarcasm, eye-rolling,
不好看的半边脸
wrong side of the face.
哦对 我发现了
Oh, yeah. Now I see it.
就是左边
Yep.
她准备好了
She's ready.
像这样
And it's this,
and it's this.
不是这样
Not this,
是这样
but this.
-好了 够了小卡 -还有这样
- Okay. Okay, that's good, Cam. -And this.
留点 留点花瓣给女儿吧
Save--let's save some petals for Lily, all right?
好 乖女儿过来
Okay. Let's do it over here, sweetheart.
-到这边来 -好的
- Right over here. - Okay.
对了 就像你走向婚礼的圣坛
There you go. Oh, like you're coming down the aisle!
一次别洒太多 不错
Not too many at once. That's good.
很好 你做得很好 乖女儿
Okay. You're doing great, Lil.
噢 她太棒了
Oh, she is, isn't she?
谁看新娘啊 咱闺女才是瞩目的焦点
Forget the bride. All the eyes are gonna be on her.
我不敢相信你居然笑出来了
I cannot believe you laughed!
抱歉 但你知道我有两个软肋笑点
I am sorry. But you know I have two weaknesses--
小孩爆粗口 老人唱饶舌
children cursing and old people rapping.
小卡 我们得告诉她那词不好
Cam, we have to tell her it's a bad word.
不行 那样只会让她觉得那词很劲爆
No. That just gives it more power.
我们越不提起这事越好
The less we make of it, the better.
我们就装作什么都没发生
Let's just pretend like it never happened.
好吧 或许 或许什么都没发生
Okay. Yeah, maybe it-- maybe it didn't.
或许是我们听错了
Maybe we--maybe we misheard.
对 或许她说的是"卡"
Yeah. Maybe she said "Truck."
或者"擦"
Or--or "Duck."
或者"菜" 她有可能说的是"草"
Or "Luck." She could have said "Yuck."
爸爸 我能吃冰淇淋吗
Daddy, can I have some ice cream?
不 宝贝儿 如果你饿了 可以吃点水果
No, honey, if you're hungry, you can have some fruit.
水果
Fruit? .
我有俩孩子要教育啊
I have two children.
菲尔 这是要上电视吗
Phil? Phil, is this televised?
我没告诉你是不想让你紧张
I didn't tell you because I didn't want to make you nervous.
好主意 真是个好主意啊
Great plan. Really good plan.
最后时刻 给我来个措手不及
Throw me for a curveball at the last minute.
别紧张妈 只是公共频道
Mom, chill. It's just public access.
我们的辩论赛也上公共频道
My debate team's on public access,
只有你们才会看而已
and the only people who watch me are you guys.
对 每次都看
Yep. All the time.
所以或许没人会看这个
So maybe nobody will see this?
不 我们想让大家看到这个
No. We want people to see this.
这样你才能当选 被人熟知才是关键
That's how you win elections. That's the whole point.
那老妈应该做些疯狂愚蠢的事
Then mom should do something so crazy and stupid.
-可以做网络红人 -妈 千万别做网络红人
- It goes viral. - Mom, please don't go viral.
好的 我会把这个加进严禁事宜中
Okay. I'll add that to my list of things not to do--
别碰脸 别翻白眼
Don't touch my face, don't roll my eyes,
别"指"点江山
don't point my fingers,
还有绝对不做网络红人
and definitely don't go viral.
你们还有谁对我有点信心的
Do any of you still believe in me?
我们当然相信你 我们站在你这边
Of course we do. We're on your side.
是右半边
The right side.
不是左边
Not the left.
我们去找个座位
Let's grab a seat.
右边 左边
Right. Left.
好了 妈 要有自信
Okay. Mom, just be confident.
凭什么 自家客厅的辩论我都输了
Based on what? I just lost a debate in my living room,
而且大家觉得我讨人嫌
and people think I'm unlikable.
那是男人针对女强人的专用词
That's just the word men use for powerful women
因为他们感觉受到威胁
because they feel threatened.
所以忘掉一切 强势不屈 舍我其谁
So just forget everything else and be proud and powerful.
你怎么这么聪明
How did you get so smart?
可能我是领养的 或是在医院抱错了
I've always assumed adoption or baby switch.
注意 不能亲吻
Hey. Hey. No kisses!
强势不屈 舍我其谁
Proud and powerful.
-抱歉 -也不能道歉
- Sorry. - And no apologizing.
对 闭嘴 赶紧进去
Yes! Shut up and get in there!
就要这个范儿
That's more like it!
对
Yeah!
天哪
Oh, god.
她来了
There she is.
-搞定他们 克莱尔 -多谢支持
- Go get 'em, Claire. -Thanks.
别担心 我们会给你助威的
Don't worry. We're going to cheer for you
不管你说了什么
no matter what you say.
真好 来自亲爱家人的更多"支持"
Oh, good. More support from my loving family.
喇叭警告 讽刺
Honk. Sarcasm.
你怎么把斯黛拉带来了
Why'd you bring Stella?
她总是往屋外跑 然后往泳池里跳
She keeps getting out and jumping in the pool.
我们可不能冒险把她留在家里 她不会游泳
We don't wanna take any chances because she can't swim.
那她为啥还老往泳池里跳
Then why does she keep jumping in the pool?
我一直在想这个问题 我有个想法
I've been thinking about it. I got a theory.
她可能有自杀倾向
She might be suicidal.
什么 这也太疯狂了吧
What? That's crazy.
这世上就没什么狗狗自杀一说
There's not such thing as doggy suicide.
你好 我是杜恩·贝利
Hi. Duane Bailey.
抱歉 我无意中听到你们谈话
Sorry. I couldn't help but overhear.
我除了是人民公仆之外
In addition to being a public servant,
还是一名获奖哈巴小猎犬饲养者
I'm also an award-winning breeder of puggles.
我赢过最佳猎犬奖 两次哟
I've won the Puggly. Twice.
我恐怕狗狗自杀是
And I'm afraid that doggy suicide
确有其事的
is all too real.
只不过主流媒体不报道罢了
It's just the mainstream media doesn't report on it,
因为不像猫艾滋那么火爆
'cause it's not as sexy as feline A.I.D.S.
斯黛拉没有自杀倾向 她就是比较脑残
Stella is not suicidal. She's just... estupid.
那 或许就是您的问题了
Well, that might be part of your problem.
她能感觉到你不喜欢她
She senses you don't like her.
你根本想不到
You have no idea.
从这个小天使踏进我们家门起
This one's been against this little angel
这位就没消停过
from the very beginning.
没错 狗狗会注意到的
Yeah, well, dogs pick up on that.
他们很敏感的
You know, they're very sensitive.
我喜欢叫他们
I like to call them, um...
填不满的情感无底洞
Bottomless pits of need.
但不能当他们的面说
But not to their face, though.
那样太伤他们感情了
That would just destroy them.
不是说你哟
Not you.
那这么说是我的错啦
So now this is my fault?
我想他知道自己在说什么
I think he knows what he's talking about.
人家可是赢过一个最佳猎犬奖的
The man won a puggly.
-两个 我赢过两个 -我们说完了
- Two. I won two pugglies. - We're done here.
-在2000年和 -是是
- In 2000- - Yeah.
你知道是哪个台播吗
Do you have any idea what station this is on?
我上网查查[上网看]
Here, I'll look online.
是网络广播吗 你早点说我就不用
It's a webcast? That would have been helpful to know
摁过九百个频道了
900 channels ago.
不是 是个公共频道之类的
No, it's on public access or something.
我要看克莱尔姑妈
I wanna watch aunt claire!
行 但是首先 宝贝 我们得谈谈
Okay. Well, first, honey, we need to talk about something.
关于你早上说的那个词
It's about that word you said this morning.
什么词
What word?
你知道 就是那个以F开头的那个词
You know, the one that starts with "F"?
-花花 -不是
- "Flower"? - No.
-果果 -不是
- "Fruit"? - No.
如果她记不起来了 我们干嘛要提醒她
If she doesn't remember it, we shouldn't remind her.
因为她说了三遍呢
Oh, well, she said it three times.
哦 你是说
Oh, you mean.
小卡 出去
Cam, leave the room!
不用 我能忍住
No. I can do this.
莉莉 那是个不好的词
Lily, that is a bad word,
而且你永远也不能再说这个词
and you are not allowed to say it ever.
但能把你逗笑呀
But it makes you laugh.
其实爸爸不应该笑的
Okay, well, daddy shouldn't be laughing,
你也永远不应该说那个词
and you should never say that word.
明白没
Do you understand?
或许吧
Maybe.
好吧 这可不是什么游戏 好吗
Okay. This is not a game, all right?
如果你再说一遍那个词
If you say that word one more time,
我就把你的玩具都没收
I'm gonna take away all your toys!
我认真的 她知道我不是认真的
I'm serious! She knows I'm not serious.
那婚礼怎么办
What about the wedding?
如果她在那说怎么办
What if she says it there?
她就像是个定时炸弹
She's like a ticking time bomb!
-那我们怎么办 取消吗 -没错
-Well, what are we gonna do, cancel? - Yes.
我们就这么说
Maybe we just call and say,
在同性婚姻合法化之前 我们不参加任何婚礼
"We're not going to any more weddings until the gays can get married."
得 咱们改走政治路线了
Oh, so now we're political?
连"同志骄傲"游行周我们都躲出去避难
We leave town on gay pride weekend
就因为不喜欢那拥挤的交通
because we don't like the traffic.
但是经验的作用是无可替代的
But there's no substitute for experience.
举例来说 我怀疑我的对手
For example, I doubt my opponent is familiar
是否熟悉镇法26-12b
with town ordinance 26-12b...
26-12b是关于噪声污染的
26-12b has to do with noise pollution--
也就是您 先生 现在正造出的哟
Something, sir, that you are guilty of right now.
她怎么这么牛掰
Oh, no she di'int!
加油 老妈
Go, mom!
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen...
看看她的眼睛
Look at her eyes.
看出来了 确实有点斗鸡眼
I know. They're a little too close together.
我已经纠结很多年了
It's been bugging me for years.
不是 她现在状态正佳
No, she's in the zone.
她已经万事俱备了
She's ready for anything.
我是很想谈谈 谈谈问题
I do like to talk... about the issues.
说起问题哈
Speaking of issues,
您先生好像有一些问题
your husband seems to have some.
抱歉
I'm sorry?
我不是在致歉 什么
I'm not sorry. What?
其实 我本不愿提起的
Oh, well, I wouldn't want to bring it up,
不过既然你问了
but since you asked, um...
在去年的二月份 您先生
In february of last year, your husband,
菲利普·邓菲 因为猥亵和淫荡行为
one, uh, Phillip Dunphy, was questioned at a local hotel
在一家本地酒店被问话
for lewd and lascivious conduct.
老天
Oh, jeez.
没这回事
That's not true.
夫人 根据这份警方报告
Ma'am, according to this police report,
他 闯进陌生人的房间
he, uh, broke into a stranger's room,
全裸的
stripped naked...
在床上摆出极为挑逗性的姿势
and then posed provocatively on the bed.
外在现象大致如此
That is technically true,
但是公平地说 那天是情人节
but in all fairness, it was valentine's day.
抱歉 那天是情人节呀
Oh! Oh, I'm so sorry. It was valentine's day.
我不太清楚
I'm not sure, uh,
您先生是不是生在这个国家
if your husband was born in this country.
也许他是非法移民吧
Perhaps he snuck in illegally,
但是在美国呢 我们在情人节这天
but here in America, we celebrate valentine's day
送人巧克力
with chocolates,
不是送人小鸡鸡
not our private parts.
这是我现在最爱的节目了
This is my new favorite show.
不是的 先生
No, sir,
他那时是在找我 他的妻子
he was looking for me, his wife,
但是他走错了房间
and he walked into the wrong room.
如果你们相信的话
If you believe that,
我有些会说话的哈巴小猎犬 很乐意卖给你们
I have some talking puggles I'd like to sell you.
你相信吗
Do you believe this?
会说话的狗 我很怀疑
Talking dogs? I'm skeptical.
-我赢过最佳猎犬奖 两次 -强硬
- I won the puggly. Twice. - Be strong.
我很高兴我的对手提起这事
I am glad that my opponent brought this up,
此事正好可以看出他的下三滥品格
as I feel that it speaks to his character
而我身正不怕影斜
more than mine.
我认为现在应该把讨论提升一个档次
I think that we should raise the level of discourse
回到那些我们的选民
and get back to the issues
真正关心的问题上来
that the voters really care about.
当他裸着的时候 你穿的什么
When he was naked, what were you wearing?
我 我认为这与本次辩论无关
I... don't think that's relevant.
你是性变态吗
Are you sex freaks?
我的个人生活和这次辩论毫无关系
My personal life has nothing to do with this.
我的对手提起这事就是为了
Uh--the--my opponent has brought this up
把公众注意力从他的政绩上转移
to distract from his own record,
因为他在六年的时间里
which shows that in--in six years,
除了制定一项"允许私人派对上
he has achieved nothing more than writing one ordinance
出现八条以上的狗"的条令之外一无所成
that allows private parties to have more than eight dogs.
简直就跟目睹兴登堡惨案一样
It's like watching the "Hindenburg."
这是我这辈子见过的最悲惨的事情了
This is the most horrible thing I've ever seen in my life.
-抱歉 -还有更惨的
- Excuse me! - Stand by.
我就是菲尔·邓菲 而且我不是变态
I am Phil Dunphy, and I am not a pervert.
我 和这镇子里很多的男士一样
I, like a lot of men in this town,
喜欢和我老婆滚床单
enjoy making love to my wife.
我是说 和他们各自的老婆滚
I mean, um... I mean with their wives.
各滚各的
Not me, them.
听着 或许我应该只是坐在那里默不作声
Look, I should probably just sit down and say nothing.
但是为时已晚
But it's too late.
我已经站起来了 很显然我也在说话
I am standing, and I'm obviously talking,
而现在你们也都盯着我看
and now you're looking at me,
我就感觉我应该继续说下去
and I feel the need to keep going.
首先一点
First of all...
没有书面的正式起诉
no charges were filed.
大家一笑而过
Everyone had a good laugh--
觉得挺滑稽 不是说笑话我
about the situation, not--not about me.
我"硬件"正常得很
Everything's fine down there.
总之
Anywho...
说到哪了
Where were we?
红遍了YouTube啊
All over YouTube.
还是做了网络红人
We went viral.
不知道哪个狗杂种给我弄了个电音版
Some sick bastard auto-tuned me.
俺
I...
和这镇子里
like a lot of men
很多的男士一样
in this town
喜欢和我老婆滚床单 滚呀么滚床单
I enjoy making love to my wife--wife
滚到天昏地暗不停歇
And I don't know how to stop.
我性放荡呀
I am a pervert.
浪里个荡
Pervert--per--
杰 曼尼
Jay! Manny!
我们早就该到那了
We should have been there already!
歌洛莉亚 我正系领带呢
Gloria, I'm tying my tie!
我穿戴搭配呢
I'm accessorizing!
比女人打扮的时间还久
And I thought I was the woman.
忘关门了
The door.
喂 斯黛拉 别啊
Ay! Estella, no! No!
别啊 别动
Ay! No! No!
斯黛拉 别想不开 别自寻短见啊
Estella, don't do it! Don't kill yourself!
你是个超级棒的狗狗
You are a perfectly fine dog!
我不讨厌你
I don't hate you!
斯黛拉 好吧 我对你是有点刻薄
Estella, okay, I was a little mean to you,
但你也不至于寻死啊
but that's no reason to kill yourself!
小年轻啊
You are young!
花花世界还有很多"闻"所未"闻"呢
You still have so much left to smell!
不
Ay!
我 我来了
I am--I go!
等着我
I'm coming!
我 曼尼
I'm--Manny!
坚持住 斯黛拉
Ay! Come on, Estella!
-咋回事 -你还好吗
- What happened? - Are you okay?
她又跳了
She did it again.
-然后你湿身救它了 -不是啊
- And you jumped in to save her? - No, Jay!
我就是赶在婚礼前小游一下啊
I wanted to take a little swim before going to the wedding!
给她条浴巾 冻得直哆嗦
Get her a towel. She's shaking like a leaf.
不不不 我意思是
Oh, no, no, I meant--
-您请用 -谢你八辈儿祖宗
- I meant-- - Thank you, Jay.
我就配条狗浴巾
The dog towel for me.
我可是你老婆啊
For the wife.
你们好
Hi!
你们好啊
Hey, guys. Hi.
好啊 有啥新鲜事没
Hi. Hey, what's shaking? What's cooking?
你们看了辩论了吧
You saw the debate, didn't you?
辩啥 那不是在
The de-what? No, that wasn't--
今天吗 是今天吧
That was today? No, no. Was that on today?
我忘了
Oh, I didn't remember.
扯谎也下点功夫好吗
You are the worst liars.
辩论实在太精彩了
It was phenomenal television.
莉莉
Oh, Lily.
多么那啥的
What a...
裙子啊
Dress.
这才哪儿跟哪儿啊
Oh, well, you ain't seen nothing yet.
开开眼 走着
How about there... we go.
我去 跟"点阵画图"似的
Yikes. She looks like a lite brite.
卢克 亲爱的
Luke, honey.
莉莉宝贝儿 做花童兴奋吗
Lily, sweetie, are you excited to be a flower girl?
是吧
Yeah?
有点小紧张
Little bit nervous?
是吧
Yeah?
她为什么不理我 她也看了辩论是吧
Why isn't she talking to me? Did she see the debate, too?
没 她被封口了
Nope, she's on verbal lockdown.
-咋了 -她整天嘴里都吧唧一个脏字
- Oh? - She's been dropping a certain curse word all day.
就是这情况 我们希望她
Mm. Yeah. Yeah, so we're just hoping
别在婚礼上口无遮拦
the next one doesn't happen during the wedding.
要是没拦住 她就是咱家今天
If it does, it'll be the second most embarrassing thing
丢死人不偿命的"二小姐"了
to happen to our family today.
菲尔 你说没那么糟糕的
Phil, you said it wasn't that bad.
车上满嘴谎言安慰你 教堂里不敢说假话
That was in the car. We're in a church now.
亲爱的
Honey...
来个人把她"灭"了吧 慎得慌
Somebody turn her off. I think I'm having a seizure.
可怜孩子
Oh, buddy.
还好 还以为会看不到莉莉登场呢
Oh, good. I thought that we were going to miss Lily.
海船都能看到她这座灯塔 你们去哪儿了
Ships at sea wouldn't miss Lily. Where have you guys been?
我跳进泳池里救那条傻狗
I had to jump in the pool to save the stupid dog...
她爱得深沉
Who she loves.
救了她不代表我爱她
That I didn't let her down doesn't mean that I love her.
"负鼠事件"后我都很少
I barely got Manny back in the pool
让曼尼下水了
after that possum incident.
我以为它溺水了
I thought it drowned,
但结果负鼠只是诈死
but turns out it was just playing possum.
没错 宝贝
Yes, papi.
好样的
Good job!
知道今天最失败的是哪部分吗
You know what the worst part of today was?
都很失败 好难选择啊
I imagine it's hard to choose.
那就是当一切一点点搞砸时
When everything was melting down,
我终于想到你问题的答案了
I realized I had an answer to your question,
为什么竞选那题
why I was running.
我想要一家子为我骄傲
I wanted to make my family proud,
不想却给家里抹了黑
and I did the exact opposite.
才不是
No.
就是 我让你们颜面扫地了
No, I did. I totally embarrassed you.
真的不是 老爸才丢人
No. No, dad embarrassed me.
我挺为你骄傲的
I was proud of you.
我特佩服你去参加竞选
I think it's cool you're running for local office.
虽然有点呆气 但我就喜欢那样的你
I mean, it's totally nerdy, and that's kind of my thing.
或许我们娘俩都一样
Hmm. Maybe it's kind of our thing.
总有一天 我会挽着你走过红毯
Ah. Some day, I'll walk you down the aisle.
只要你没"浪"入班房
If you're not in perv jail.
请各位就座
Please be seated.
朋友们 亲人们 谢谢大家前来...
Friends, family, thank you for making...
不是吧你
Really?
我逢婚必哭的
Well, you know I cry at weddings.
别啊
Oh, no.
-怎么了 -把眼泪咽进肚子里
- What? - Stop--stop crying.
你自己蛇蝎冷血 空洞无情
Well, just because you have ice water in your veins,
-不代表... -别 别 莉莉
- doesn't mean that-- - No. No, Lily...
打住 莉莉
No. Lily...
他好着呢 爸爸好着呢
He's fine. Daddy's fine.
-爸爸高兴着呢 -爸爸 爸爸
- Daddy's not sad. - Daddy, daddy!
看见没 我说很搞笑的吧
You see? I told you it was funny.
对不住了
Excuse us.
恭喜你们
Congratulations.
应该没问题了 冲吧 像小汽艇一样
There. That ought to do it.. Go on, you little motorboat!
游得多欢啊
Look at her go!
她去哪儿
Where's she going?
天呐 她不是要把自己塞进
Oh, jeez, I think she's trying to get herself
过滤器里吧
sucked into the filter.
你又说什么刺激她了
What'd you say to her?
我什么都没说啊
I didn't say anything!
等等
Wait a second.
杰 你瞧
Jay, look.
看吧 她没有想自寻短见
See? She was not trying to kill herself.
她只是想去拿小捏捏来着
She was just trying to get to the squeaky wiener!
这可以解释她的几连跳了
That must be why she's been jumping in.
那玩意儿肯定一直在那 真逗
It must have been there all the time. That's hilarious!
是啊
Ay, si!
逗你个头
No, it's not!
现在看不逗
Not now.
将来再看就逗了
I'm saying it will be.
将来
Later.